http://www.inyopools.com/privacy.aspx

My Account
FREE Shipping over $50!
INYO Pools Privacy Policy
Inyo Pool Products Inc. is committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information Inyo Pool Products Inc. collects through our web site at www.inyopools.com ("Site") is used only in the manner and for the purposes described in this Inyo Pool Products Inc. Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy").
User Consent to Privacy Policy
Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using the Site, either manually or via an automated device or program, shall be considered a "User." All Users are bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. Users consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable User information ("Information") pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Information Collected from Users
Inyo Pool Products Inc. collects the email address of Users that email a question or comment to Inyo Pool Products Inc. or submit a customer review.
Inyo Pool Products Inc. collects the billing and shipping addresses, including relevant e-mail, phone and credit card numbers and expiration dates of Users who purchase a product from Inyo Pool Products Inc. through the Site. This includes Users who register to become Inyo Pool Products Inc. members or enter any Inyo Pool Products Inc. contests or other promotional features available on the Site. Inyo Pool Products Inc. does not store a User's credit card information, meaning this information must be re-entered each time an item is purchased.
Through the use of "cookies" (For more information regarding Cookies, see below), Inyo Pool Products Inc. may collect and store anonymous information relating to Users' browsing patterns, including, for instance, the User's browser version, site referral information, IP address, operating system, and other technical Site use information.
Cookies
The Site uses a feature of Internet Web browsers called a Cookie, which is a file that a User's Web browser places on a User's computer's hard drive, to assign an identification code to the computer and to collect anonymous browsing information. On this Site, cookies are used in conjunction with session variables to track a User's shopping cart and expire as soon as an order is completed or if a shopping cart sits idle for a lengthy period without being checked-out.
Inyo Pool Products Inc. does not use Cookies to retrieve Information about Users from a User's computer unless the User knowingly and willingly provided such Information. For instance, Inyo Pool Products Inc.’s cookies do not collection any Information and the cookies do not collect, store or contain any credit card information.
You may set your Internet Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent. If you prevent a cookie from being sent, you may limit the functionality Inyo Pool Products Inc. can provide you when you visit the Site, especially when purchasing an item on the Site.
Use of Information
Inyo Pool Products Inc. uses the Information collected from its Users to:
** Respond to Users' questions or comments; ** Administer a User's contest entry or entry in other promotional feature; ** Fulfill a User's purchase request and notify Users of their order status; and ** Provide Users with important functionality changes to the Site, new Inyo Pool Products Inc. services and special offers we think you will find valuable.
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Unless we have your consent or except as required or permitted by law, Inyo Pool Products Inc. will not sell, share, trade or give away any Information that it collects or receives regarding its Users. Inyo Pool Products Inc. may disclose information about our Users to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Inyo Pool Products Inc. or others. Inyo Pool Products Inc. may disclose Information to third party in the event that a third party acquires Inyo Pool Products Inc. or its assets. (See, Sale or Acquisition section below.)
Linked Internet Web Sites
The Site may provide hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or may take you to a third party website not controlled by Inyo Pool Products Inc.. These hyperlinked third party websites may collect and disclose Information different than this Site. Inyo Pool Products Inc. is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites, and Inyo Pool Products Inc. expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.
Children
The Inyo Pool Products Inc. Site is not directed towards children under 18 years of age and Inyo Pool Products Inc. does not knowingly collect any information from children under 18 years of age through the Site.
Security
Inyo Pool Products Inc. has security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control, including credit card information that is submitted to Inyo Pool Products Inc. When Users place orders or access their account information, the Site uses secure server software (SSL), which encrypts all information Users' input before it is sent to us. Thus, we have taken steps to protect the Information we collect from you from unauthorized access. Unfortunately, no system is perfect; therefore, Inyo Pool Products Inc. makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. Inyo Pool Products Inc. shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Policy because of a security breach or technical malfunction.
Sale or Acquisition
In the event that another company acquires Inyo Pool Products Inc. or all or part of its assets, we reserve the right to include Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.
Applicable Law/International Issues
In the event that another company acquires Inyo Pool Products Inc. or all or part of its assets, we reserve the right to include Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.
Amendments to Privacy Policy
Inyo Pool Products Inc. reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Use of Information that Inyo Pool Products Inc. gathers now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the Information is used. Any amendments made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on the Site.
Home
Privacy
